In this video I am going to talk about if brother
your Money EMI auto debit has failed
then brother
how will you be able to pay your Money EMI with the help of your phone, watch this video
completely and you have to understand everything,
in this video I am going to show you everything live
brother how you have to
pay your Money EMI, whatever
is there here I am going to show you everything through live process, that is why I am
requesting you to
watch the video completely and you have to
understand everything, see brother what happens here, the
EMI of Money which auto debits here
fails or brother this problem comes from Money's side,
brother the
problem comes from your bank's side.  So brother,
suppose your RT debit EMI
fails here and brother,
EMI is not deducted from your bank account.  You then have to
pay the due charges here later.
So I will show you everything live here.
How brother, you have to check here whether
your EMI will be automatically disabled
or not and how brother, if it has been disabled
then how can you pay it.  I am also going to
show you all this by doing the live process.
Before that please like the video.  Please
subscribe to the channel
because you keep getting such information on my channel.  Okay, I'm on the
phone.  I am going to
show you everything by flag processing.
Let's go here.  You
can see here that it is showing on the side.
I have turned on the screenshot of my phone here
and I am directly going to my Money
app.  Ok?  Here you
can see that
I am directly opening the Manib application.  Brother, I myself have taken a
loan here.  I am showing you
how brother, you have to check yourself here.
First of all brother, where your loan will be shown.
Loan Bhai will show you here
in instant loan.  Ok?  You can see it here.  You have to
click on this.  Insta
loan here, like brothers, click on this.
Now brother, you can see it here.  You
can check everything from here.  Ok?
I am cutting here brother, where am
I showing here.  You can see this
here brother, first of all you have to check whether
whatever is enabled or disabled here,
brother, even if it is enabled for you, your EI will not be
deducted, this is also Mani's fault.  If brother,
your account is disabled here, then
if your EMI is not deducted here, then it means that there is some
problem from your side.
Your auto debit is disabled.  Whether there is a
problem from the bank's side or any other problem.
Brother, the problem is from your side.  See,
here many people
set auto debit to their money through UPI.  Many
people set up through ATM card.
Many people set up through Aadhar card.
So here brother, if the ATM card is
inspired then your auto debit will be
disabled.  If you have
set up UPI, then you must have uninstalled PhonePe or
Google Pay through which you set it up, so
your auto debit through it must have been disabled here.
Correct?  It happens through that also.  Correct?
Now, brothers who have made Aadhar card, sometimes
due to problem in Aadhar card or
problem in the bank, your auto
debit gets disabled here.  Here
brother, if your auto debit is enabled then there is
no problem.  Everything is fine.  Even if
your EID is not deducted brother, I will tell you how you can pay the
EMI.  If the brother
is disabled then he can also get it enabled here.
I have made a proper video for you.
You will find the video here at the end of this video.
Click there and watch it.
How
can you enable auto debit of your money view here brother?
If your brother is disabled then you
can understand by watching the video.  Okay, or
go and visit the channel, brother, you will find videos, after
watching them you will be able to understand everything,
brother, if your auto debit of Money View
is disabled here, then you will be able to enable it,
now brother, whatever is there here, you
can see it here, your enable/disable is
here.  Now brother, how
can we pay the EMI of whatever is there here?
To pay EMI you have to click on this.
You will click here.  Ok
?  You can see it here.  Like I'm clicking.
You also have to click here.
Brother, please click here.  Here
my own brother's auto debit was disabled here.
I have enabled it by tracking it here.
Ok?  What to do here now
?  You can see it directly here.   You have to
click on Chat with this.  We will click on this.  You
can see it here.
I am showing it here.  As you click here.
Now you have to fill up here.
EMI payment here, whatever
your EMI payment is, you
can see it here, if it is failed then you can see it here.
Here you have to write something like EMI Auto Debit Payment
Failed EI.  You can
see it here, whatever happens, you can see it here.  We will
write to you on EMI here.
I am showing you.  You
can check the EMI here.  You
can see where it went here.  You have to do this here and
screenshot.  Now brother, you can see it here.
You will get the option.  Here you can see how much
EMI you have to pay.  You can see here Pay
Now, by clicking on this whatever
your EMI will be, you will directly click on it.
You can pay your EMI here.
No problem.  You
can see everything here.  By clicking on this,
you can pay EMI in one or two clicks.
Now I will tell you here that mine has been activated.
Ok?  Here I have done it.  Are
you fine?  Now you are closing it here.
Brother, everything is fine with me.
So here, whatever auto debit or
payment issue there is, brother, you will get many
options.  By clicking here,
brother, you
can pay all your EMIs here.  EMI
Payment Failed: You are getting the option here.  You
can see it here.
By clicking on this you can pay your EMI directly here.
No problem.
I am showing it here right now.  Brother, I was facing the same
problem and brother, you have to
upload the screenshot here, which will be your
screenshot.  And brother, your EMI will be paid
directly here.  You
will upload the screenshot here and brother, you will get the
option to pay.  You can see it here.
Whatever disabled EMI was there here like my auto
debit.  You can see the manual
payment here.  You can see here that
he
gave me the link to make the payment here.  You
can pay your EMI by clicking on Direct Pay.
Now let's talk about this brother, we will
not be able to pay our first EMI.  Brother, you will have to
pay the EMI later.  Like
your Bhai Day has passed, brother, you
can go here and get help from them.  You can generate your link
and pay EMI directly from here.
If brother, you think that
I should pay the EMI first, then brother, you
cannot pay the EMI first.  My brother, the
EMI date is 5th April so I
cannot pay it now.  Okay, okay?  Because my
auto debit is enabled here.  I
can take a foreclosed loan but
cannot pay EMI here.  So brother, if
your brother's EMI has failed, then
brother, by going to Help here, you
can get the link of your EMI and by
clicking on Pay, you can make the payment directly here.
Like brother, when you make the payment, it will
show on your application within 24 hours and
not brother, it will show instantly.  If you wait for 24 hours, then
after that it will be done on your
application and your EI.
You can pay now but it takes
24 hours for the update to happen.  So brother, in
this way you will be able to solve the payment failure problem of your Money View.
In which
everything was shown to you through live process.   If you like the
video then please like it.
Subscribe to the new channel.  If brother has any
doubt, he can comment.